George List papers, 1894-2008 C424
Indiana University Archives
George List papers
1894-2008
1958-1990
Indiana University Archives
List, George, 1911-2008
C424
16 cubic feet 18 boxes
Collection consists of the papers of George List (1911-2008), Professor of Folklore, Director of the Inter-American Program in Ethnomusicology (1966-1976), and Director of the Archives of Traditional Music (1954-1976) at Indiana University. His primary research interests included folk music, the traditional music of the Hopi tribes of Northern Arizona, and the music of indigenous tribes in the Caribbean regions of Colombia and the Andes and Amazon regions of Ecuador. This collection includes personal and professional correspondence, publications, research, subject files, audiovisual content, and many of his musical compositions.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Advance notice required.
Biographical Note
George List was born George Harold Lisitsky in Tucson, Arizona in 1911. In 1933, he graduated from The Julliard School with a diploma in flute performance, and in 1941, earned a Bachelor's degree in music education from Columbia University. After completing a Master's in the same field at Columbia in 1945, he went onto earn a PhD in music theory with minors in composition and education from Indiana University in 1954. Throughout his life, List remained active as a musician, composer, and scholar of ethnomusicology and folklore.
Before entering academia, List had a career as a school music teacher in New York City. In 1934, he established and directed the Madison Square Boys Club, a music school for underprivileged children in Manhattan. From 1939-1943, List remained in New York, teaching and directing several orchestras and bands in public school systems, as well as conducting for the International Workers Order. During this time, he was also active as a performing flutist in New York and Denver, and also published several compositions for flute, piano, voice, orchestra, and band.
List began his academic career as an Instructor of Music at Colorado College from 1945-1946, then quickly became Assistant Professor (1946-1948) and Associate Professor (1948-1953) of music at Miami University in Ohio. He moved to Indiana University in 1954, where he remained until his retirement in 1976. During this time, he was prominent in the establishment of the Archives of Traditional Music and the Ethnomusicology program.
During his time at Indiana University, List taught courses in folk music, music, anthropology, and folklore, and served as Director of the Archives of Traditional Music from 1954-1976 and Director of the Inter-American Program in Ethnomusicology at Indiana University from 1966-1976. His primary research interests included folk music, the traditional music of the Hopi tribes of Northern Arizona, as well as the music of indigenous tribes in the Caribbean regions of Colombia and the Andes and Amazon regions of Ecuador. Some of his notable publications include Cantos Costeños, Folksongs of the Atlantic Coastal Region of Colombia (1973), Music and Poetry in a Colombian Village: A Tri-Cultural Heritage (1983), Singing About It: Folksong in Southern Indiana (1991), and Stability and Variation in Hopi Song (1993). He also founded and edited the periodical The Folklore and Folkmusic Archivist and created and narrated the television program Music in the Life of Man, produced by the Indiana University Department of Radio and Television.
List's most prominent contributions to Indiana University were his involvement in developing the ethnomusicology program and his tenure as Director of the Archives of Traditional Music. Since ethnomusicology was not yet an established field, List began his career as a lecturer in folk music, anthropology, and the recording and transcripting of traditional music. In 1964, he was appointed an associate professor in the Department of Folklore. In 1966, with the help of a grant from the Ford Foundation, List established and taught in the Inter-American Program in Ethnomusicology within the Folklore Department. This program specialized in the traditional music of the Americas, Europe, and Africa, only the third program of this type in existence at the time.
Between 1954-1976, List also served as the Director of the Archives of Traditional Music. During this time, he formulated policies and procedures for the processing and use of the collections, making them accessible to researchers. His contributions were instrumental in turning the archives into an internationally known public research resource. Additionally, he was one of the first people to create practices for archiving and cataloging these types of materials, and some of his procedures served as models for similar music archives, such as those at UCLA.
List retired from Indiana University in 1977 due to the onset of blindness caused by glaucoma. Despite his retirement, he remained active in the field of ethnomusicology, writing books, obtaining research grants, giving lectures, staying active in professional organizations, and publishing articles up to the age of ninety-one. List passed away on September 28, 2008 at the age of 97.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into seven series: Biographical, Correspondence and subject files, Publications, Research, Professional, Compositions, and Audiovisual.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of George List are arranged into seven series: Biographical, Correspondence and subject files, Publications, Research, Professional, Compositions, and Audiovisual. Most files are labeled and arranged based on the order in which they were received from List. His earlier papers are clearly labeled and dated, but materials from the late 1970s to 2008, the time period in which List was blind and depended upon others to organize his papers, are less clearly labeled, not uniform, and often undated. These materials are arranged chronologically after List's own organization based on their appropriate series.
This collection spans 1924-2008, with the bulk of the materials dating from 1958-1990. Materials are centered around List's early career as a music teacher and composing musician, as well as his academic career, including research on indigenous South American music, publications, and papers relating to his work with the Archives of Traditional Music. Also included are personal and professional correspondence, a full publication list, poetry and short stories by List, and original musical compositions. Works of note include full instrumentation for Marche O'Malley, a symphony composed by List and performed in 1947 and 1951, and articles "The Boundaries of Speech and Song" (Ethnomusicology 1961) and "The Reliability of Transcription" (Ethnomusicology 1974).
The Biographical series (1924-2006) is arranged alphabetically and contains items from List's career as a music teacher, published biographies, newspaper clippings, and publicity materials about his accomplishments. It also includes his curriculum vitae, tenure and retirement information, and a memoir written in 2004.
Correspondence and subject files (1933-2008) are combined and organized alphabetically. The Professional correspondence and subject files subseries contains correspondence with co-workers, colleagues, and institutions regarding List's professional career, as well as information about publishers, libraries, and museums affiliated with List. The Personal correspondence and subject files subseries consists of correspondence with friends, family, and colleagues that is more personal in nature and less related to List's career. The series is organized based on List's original order, resulting in some overlap between professional and personal correspondence.
The Publications series (1946-2005) includes drafts and revisions of book chapters and articles, unpublished manuscripts, and all articles published by List between 1946-1992. Also included are reviews written by List between 1960-1986, as well as reviews of his own works written by others. Materials are first arranged in the order created by List, with other materials arranged after them in chronological order. Items of note include the manuscripts for Cuentos Costeños, and Mozart and Tonality, both of which were never published.
Research files (1894, 1953-2006) mainly consist of List's research related to the music of the indigenous people of Ecuador, Colombia, and Venezuela, as well as his research from 1960 and 1963 about the Hopi tribe in the southwestern United States. Also included are lists of musical tracks and transcriptions used for various TV and radio productions with which List was involved, and materials used in lectures. Materials are organized as received from List. This series contains a set of numbered folders titled List-##, which largely consist of track listings for radio spots, television programs, and demo tapes. Also contained are two sets of index cards, the first which is numerically ordered contains supplementary notes which correspond to the numbered List folders in Boxes 11 and 17, the second contains citations for articles written by List as well as those he used for research purposes.
The Professional series (1942-2004) includes materials from conferences attended by List, correspondence with the Society for Ethnomusicology (SEM), teaching materials, faculty reports, and papers about grants and fellowships List received or applied for. Items are arranged as received from List, with conferences and correspondence listed chronologically and grants and fellowships organized alphabetically.
The Compositions series (1926-2008) consists of musical compositions composed by List for piano, organ, mixed chorus, flute, clarinet, oboe, viola, cello, and orchestra. Also included are compact discs of his music being performed, and a vinyl record of "Andante for Woodwind Quintette." Other works of note include Gadgets: A Commercial Opera, and a full score with orchestral parts for Marche O'Malley. Most of these works were never published and are undated. Pieces are arranged alphabetically.
Audiovisual materials (1941-1985) include a set of 108 cassette tape albums titled "Letters," 13 reels of open reel tape titled "Copies of cuentos from Colombia," an open reel tape of a WTIU Broadcast about student activities and boycott meetings from 1969, and an undated VHS tape titled Conjunto de Cumbio. Items are arranged according to List's labels.
All photographs and negatives were removed and are housed with the Indiana University Archives photo collection. Consult with the Archives Photographs Curator for further information.
Separated Material
Accession records and catalog listings for the Archives of Traditional Music were separated and sent to the Archives of Traditional Music. Sheet music by composers other than George List were sent to the William & Gayle Cook Music Library.
Photographs Pulled: Photographs were separated and sent to the Indiana University Photo Archives.
132 photographs were removed from this collection. Most are images of indigenous musicians and musical instruments gathered as part of List's research in Thailand, South America, and with the Hopi tribe in the United States. Hopi photographs include 41 images of dolls made by tribe members. Many photographs were used in List's publications.
Related Material
Additional publications and research materials may be accessed in IUScholarworks
Related photographs may be available in the University Archives Photographs Database
Additional information and recordings may be available at the Indiana University Archives of Traditional Music
Acquisition Information
Accession numbers: 2005/004, 2008/099
Provenance
Dr. List's memoir given to the Archives by him in 2005; remainder of papers transferred after his death in 2008.
Appraisal
Items found in duplicates, such as drafts, publications, transcriptions, and programs, were weeded from this collection. Personal documents, such as bills, bank statements, interlibrary loan forms, medical records, report cards, and transcripts were also discarded. Publications and compositions by people other than George List were weeded. A sampling of exams from a notation seminar was retained and the rest discarded.
Ethnomusicologists --Indiana --Bloomington.; List, George, 1911-2008 -- Archives; List, George, 1911-2008 -- Correspondence; Indiana University, Bloomington. Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology -- Faculty -- Archives
- Biographical, 1924-2006; undated (Box 1)
  - Biographies (Box 1)
    - Directories, 1965-1974 (Box 1)
    - Encyclopaedia Judaica, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Boys Club Madison Square, 1936-1937 (Box 1)
  - Bronx Children's Music School Project, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Childhood School Materials, 1924-1926 (Box 1)
  - Clippings, 1959-1965 (Box 1)
  - Concert Programs, 1937-1991 (Box 1)
  - Conducting, 1936-1949 (Box 1)
  - Contracts IU, 1954-1978 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence and Publicity, 1967-1991 (Box 1)
  - Curriculum Vitae (Box 1)
    - 1964-1981 (Box 1)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - 2004 (Box 1)
    - 2005 (Box 1)
  - Employment Record at IU, 2002 (Box 1)
  - English Class Writings, 1940 (Box 1)
  - Ideas, Sketches, 1940 (Box 1)
  - Indiana University Certificate of Retirement, 1977 (Box 1)
  - IU Retirement, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Julliard Graduation, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Ladybug, undated (Box 1)
  - Let's Build a Town play and music score, directed by List, 1930 (Box 1)
  - Living Will, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Madison Square Boys Club, 1936-1937 (Box 1)
  - Marche O'Malley Publicity, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Meadow Ridge, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Memoir p. 2077-2168, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Miami University Programs, 1948 (Box 1)
  - "Ngo and Lithla," "Little Blarney," stories by George List, undated (Box 1)
  - Obituary, undated (Box 1)
  - The Obstacle Course: A Musical Memoir by George List, p. 1-99, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Perkins School, Howe Press (Brailler Machine), 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Playlets, Poems, Stories, undated (Box 1)
  - Poem to the Editor, Herald Telephone, April 1971 (Box 1)
  - Poem, "We Who Live" by List, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Poems and Stories by List, undated (Box 1)
  - Programs, 1945-1957 (Box 1)
  - Programs, Dayton Art Institute, Miami University, Columbia University, 1944-1952 (Box 1)
  - Programs, Flute, 1934-1953 (Box 1)
  - Programs, Miscellaneous Recitals and Concerts, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Programs, Public Schools, 1943-1954 (Box 1)
  - Publicity, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Rhythm Band Parts, 1937 (Box 1)
  - A Short Memoir, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Tenure, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Unrevised Short Memoir, 2004 (Box 1)
- Correspondence and subject files, 1933-2008; undated (Box 1)
  - Professional correspondence and subject files, 1946-2008; undated (Box 1)
    - Ashton Letters, 1956-1960 (Box 1)
    - Blindness, 1987; 1990 (Box 1)
    - Blizzard, Alan Maeve, Obituary, 2007 (Box 1)
    - Copyright Gadgets, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
      - General, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
      - Cantos Costenos, Tony Seeger and Ruth Stone, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
    - Flutes Insurance, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Graf, Marilyn, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Grove's Dictionary (Box 1)
      - General (Box 1)
        - 1976 (Box 1)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box 1)
        Separated Materials
        (8 photographs removed)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1985 (Box 1)
    - H, 1978-1993 (Box 1)
    - Hasse, John, 1983-1991 (Box 1)
    - Henderson, Eri, 1951-1995 (Box 1)
    - Herndon, Marcia, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
    - Herzog, George, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - Hickerson, Joseph, 1982; 1992 (Box 1)
    - Hopi (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
      - Shaul - Text, Transcriptions, 1992 (Box 1)
      - General, 2005 (Box 1)
    - Hornbostel Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 1)
    - House Plans, 1965 (Box 1)
    - I, 1964-1994 (Box 2)
    - Indiana Folk Music (article on "Amish" by Umble), undated (Box 2)
    - Indiana Office of Social Services, 1981-1983 (Box 2)
    - Indiana State Library, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Indiana University - Financial Guidelines, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Indiana University Foundation, 1979-1983 (Box 2)
    - Indiana University Museum, 1976-1994 (Box 2)
    - Indiana University News Bureau News Releases, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Indiana University Press, 1982-1992 (Box 2)
    - International Folk Music Council, 1961-1968 (Box 2)
    - J, 1963-1991 (Box 2)
    - Journal of the American Musicological Society (JAMS), 1984-1985 (Box 2)
    - K, 1977-1987 (Box 2)
    - Kahane, Mariana Rudinovics, 1968-1994 (Box 2)
    - Katz, Israel Joe (Box 2)
      - General, 1979-1991 (Box 2)
      - Includes cassette tape of Judeo-Spanish Ballad Examples, 2005 (Box 2)
    - Kent State University Press, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    - Keyboard Junior, 1964-1979 (Box 2)
    - Krader, Barbara, 1987; 1989 (Box 2)
    - Kubik, Gerhard, 1981-1990 (Box 2)
    - L, 1979-1994 (Box 2)
    - Levine Correspondence, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Library of Congress, 1976-1992 (Box 2)
    - Library – Indiana University, 1986-1994 (Box 2)
    - Lilly Foundation, undated (Box 2)
    - Lisitsky, C.E., 1975-1984 (Box 2)
    - Lisitsky, Gen, 1960-1970 (Box 2)
    - McCarthy Era Photocopies, 1953-1954 (Box 2)
    - McIntire, Nan, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Miami University, 1952-1953 (Box 2)
    - Music Contract, 2007 (Box 2)
    - Niketia, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Oxford University Press, 2005 (Box 2)
    - Photo, 1978; undated (Box 2)
      (5 photographs and negative removed)
    - Pimentel, Augustin Diaz, 1980-1985 (Box 2)
    - Piñeros Translation, 1985-1995 (Box 2)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 2)
    - Prison, 1992 (Box 2)
    - Proposals, undated (Box 2)
    - Publishing (Box 2)
      - Around Our House, 1959-1973 (Box 2)
      - Associated Music Publishers, 1941-1982 (Box 2)
      - Boundaries of Speech and Song - Demonstration Tape, 1980 (Box 2)
      - Children's Piano Pieces, 1959-1962 (Box 2)
      - Comp - Boosey & Hawkes, 1948-1953 (Box 2)
      - Compositions, 1946-1963 (Box 2)
      - Contracts and Royalties, 1946-1973 (Box 2)
      - Folk Song in Southern Indiana, 1991 (Box 2)
      - Letters, 2001 (Box 2)
      - Little Suite for Piano, Letters to Publishers, 1950-1958 (Box 2)
    - R, 1977-1991 (Box 2)
    - Radio and Television, 1955-1968 (Box 2)
    - Ramon y Rivera, Luis Felipe and his wife (Isabel Aretz), 1993 (Box 2)
    - Recording for the Blind, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - Research and Graduate Development Money and Grants, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Richmond, W. Edson, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Répertoire International de Littérature Musicale (RILM) Abstracts, 1975-1994 (Box 2)
    - Robertson, Carol, 1982-1992 (Box 2)
    - Rowell, Lewis, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Russian Ethnomusicologists, undated (Box 2)
    - S, 1977-1995 (Box 2)
    - Sadie, Stanley, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Satterwhite, Marc (Box 2)
      - 1988-1992 (Box 2)
      - 1986-1994 (Box 2)
      - 2005 (Box 2)
    - Schwartz, Deborah, 1982-1995 (Box 2)
    - Seaman, David, 1979-1986 (Box 2)
    - Sebeok, 1955-1968 (Box 2)
    - Seeger, Tony, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
    - Seitz, Barb and Harold, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Seminar - List Discussion Group, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Sewell, Helen, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Shelly, Jane - Editor, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Singer, Roberta (Bobbi), 1977-1992 (Box 2)
    - Speech and Melody, Ann Bahr, 1991 (Box 2)
    - T, 1982-1991 (Box 2)
    - Tadlock, Paula (Ralph), 1982 (Box 2)
    - Texas University, 1985 (Box 2)
    - To-Do List, undated (Box 2)
    - Totten, Nancy, 1991-1994 (Box 2)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1996 (Box 2)
    - V, 1980; 1983; 1990 (Box 2)
    - Vandor, Ivan, 1983 (Box 2)
    - VIP (Bloomington), 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - W, 1981-1992 (Box 2)
    - Wachsman, Klaus, 1978-1982 (Box 2)
    - Warren-Findley, Jannell, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
    - Wirt, Monica, 1970-1987 (Box 2)
  - Personal correspondence and subject files, 1933-2004; undated (Box 3)
    - A, 1969-1974 (Box 3)
    - Abbott, William, 1959-1982 (Box 3)
    - Archives - Old Brochure, undated (Box 3)
    - B (Box 3)
    - Bain, Wilfred C., 1954-1972 (Box 3)
    - Behague, Gerard, 1977-1980 (Box 3)
    - Bennett, Jo, undated (Box 3)
    - Blacking, John, 1971-1981 (Box 3)
    - Boilés, Charles L., 1973-1976 (Box 3)
    - C, 1968-1971 (Box 3)
    - Caballero, Winston, 1968-1975 (Box 3)
    - Cáceras, Abraham, 1976-1984 (Box 3)
    - Card, Caroline, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
    - Carter, Byrum E., 1970 (Box 3)
    - Carvalho-Neto, Paulo de, 1963-1975 (Box 3)
    - Cazden, Norman, 1958-1971 (Box 3)
    - Chamorro, Arturo, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Chase, Gilbert, 1963-1966 (Box 3)
    - Christensen, Dieter, 1967-1974 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Ronald, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Colombia - Fulbright Commission, 1967-1975 (Box 3)
    - Columbia University, Dean, Graduate Faculties, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Computer -IU, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Corrêa de Azevedo, Luis Heitor, 1964-1985 (Box 3)
    - Crabbs, Dean Richard F., 1969 (Box 3)
    - Crossley-Holland, Peter, 1965-1969 (Box 3)
    - Curtis, Richard, 1965-1969 (Box 3)
    - D, 1959-1976 (Box 3)
      (1 photograph removed)
    - Daguet, Pierre, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Daniel, Ralph, 1967-1971 (Box 3)
    - Dannemann R., Manuel, 1964-1972 (Box 3)
    - Day, Harry, 1967 (Box 3)
    - De Lerma, Dominique, 1970-1973 (Box 3)
    - Dorson, Dick, 1970 (Box 3)
    - E, 1960-1968 (Box 3)
    - Ehrlichman, Milton and Joy (Box 3)
    - Emsheimer, Ernst, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Erdely, Stephen - Dissertation, Etc., 1962-1965 (Box 3)
    - Etheridge, Beth, 1963 (Box 3)
    - European Trip, May-June 1960 (Box 3)
    - Extension (University), 1957 (Box 3)
    - F (Box 3)
    - Faculty Handbook, 1955-1965 (Box 3)
    - Fishers, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
    - Fogal, Robert, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
    - Folklore Department, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Forms, Announcements, etc., 1959-1961 (Box 3)
    - Fraboschi, Elena, 1969-1975 (Box 3)
    - Frankel, Eran, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
    - Franson, Sonya, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Frisbie, Charlotte, 1975 (Box 3)
    - G, 1960-1977 (Box 3)
    - García de Giego, Pilar, 1970-1975 (Box 3)
    - George, Michael M., 1966 (Box 3)
    - Gerson-Kiwi, Dr. (Mrs.) Edith, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Gillis, Frank and Ruth, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Gisela, 1980; 1985 (Box 3)
    - González Paz, Dr. Emiro, 1965; 1985 (Box 3)
    - Graduate School (Box 3)
      - General (Box 3)
        - 1968 (Box 3)
        - 1968-1972 (Box 3)
      - David Herring, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Graf, Walter, 1970-1973 (Box 3)
    - Grame, Theodore, 1964-1969 (Box 3)
    - Grebe, María Ester, 1967-1980 (Box 3)
    - H, 1955-1976 (Box 3)
    - Hand, Wayland, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Harrington, Ross D., 1968 (Box 3)
    - Hasse, John E., 1975 (Box 3)
    - Haywood, Charles, 1959-1975 (Box 3)
    - Hedblom, Folke, 1964-1967 (Box 3)
    - Heffner, Ray L., 1965 (Box 3)
    - Heins, Ernst, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Henderson, Eric, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Herzog, George - Correspondence, 1935-1976 (Box 3)
    - Hilda (last name unknown), 1952 (Box 3)
    - Hodge, Carleton T., 1968 (Box 3)
    - Hoff, Earl W., 1966 (Box 3)
    - Hofman, Shlomo, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Honsa, Vladimir, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Hoyo, Nieves de, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
    - Hudson, Herman (Vice-Chancellor), 1971 (Box 3)
    - Hurt, Wesley, 1970 (Box 3)
    - I, 1958-1980 (Box 3)
    - Icelandic (Sheridan Schroeter), 1960-1964 (Box 3)
    - Indiana Composers Guild, Indiana Federation of Music Clubs, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Indiana University, 1967; 1987-1992 (Box 3)
    - Inter-American Brochures, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
    - International Affairs Center, 1966-1971 (Box 3)
    - Instruments in I.U. Museum, 1972 (Box 3)
    - IU Folksong Club, 1963 (Box 3)
    - J, 1959-1972 (Box 3)
    - Jane (last name unknown), 2004 (Box 3)
    - Jenkins, Jean Lynn, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
    - Jhong Bok-Joo, 1973-1976 (Box 3)
    - Jones, A.M., 1969-1971 (Box 3)
    - K, 1960-1977 (Box 3)
    - Kagan, Alan L., 1967 (Box 3)
    - Kamol Kedusiri, 1957; undated (Box 3)
      (9 photographs)
    - Karabey, Mrs. Laika, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Katz, Israel J., 1971-1979 (Box 3)